Guide to the Robert J. Levine Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1965-2007; Accession 2009-M-018
  - Correspondence
    - Burroughs Wellcome, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Burrow, Gerard, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
    - Burt, Mary Jane, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Burt, Robert, 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
    - Byck, Robert, 1977-1986 (Box 3, Folder 28-30)
    - Byrne, Tom, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Cadman, Ed, 1988-1997 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Oncology, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Calabresi, Guido, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Callahan, Daniel, 1979-1997 (Box 3, Folder 35-37)
    - Cambridge University Press, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Canada Medical Research Council (MRC), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
    - Canadian Medical Association, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Cantor, Norman, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Caplan, Arthur, 1980-1995 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Capron, Alex, 1972-1993 (Box 3, Folder 44-46)
    - CardioGenesis, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 47-48)
    - Carlini, E. A., 2001 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Carpenter, Charles, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Carpenter, Tom, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Carpenter, Will: Placebo, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Carroll, Greg, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Carson, Ronald, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Cash payments to SS, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Casolino, Marie, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Cassel, Chris, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Cassel, Eric, 1982-1992 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Cattorini, Paolo, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Research on AIDS, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 61-62)
    - Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Pregnant women, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Chadwick, Gary, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Chalmers, Tom, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Charney, Dennis, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - Charo, Alfa, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Charon, Rita, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chastain, Garvin and R. Eric Landrum, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chesney, Margaret, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Childress, James F., 1977-1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - China Medical Board, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Chiron, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Cho, Mildred, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Choice in Dying, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Chou, Willis, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Christakis, Nicholas, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Chugunova, Nina, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Chuong, Robert, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Churchill, Larry, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Circe, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Citizen Ambassador Program, 1994-1998 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
    - Clayton, Ellen Wright, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Clinical Information Confidentiality Committee, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Clinical Research Center: Children, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Clinical Scholars, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Cnaan, Avital, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Cohen, Carl, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Cohen, Cynthia, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Cohen, Donald, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Cohen, Lawrence (Larry), 1970-1996 (Box 4, Folder 30-32)
    - Cohen, S., 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Cohn, Sarah, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Collaborative Ocular Melanoma Study, 1993-2002 (Box 4, Folder 35-37)
    - Columbia Institute, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
    - Coming to Medicine, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Comroe, Julius, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Conferences on Health and Human Values, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Conn, Harold, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
    - Connecticut Hospital Association (CHA), 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Connecticut United for Research Excellence (CURE), 1992-2000 (Box 4, Folder 48-49)
    - Cook, Rebecca, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Cooper, Ellen, Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Cooper Hospital, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Cooper, Jeffrey, Circa 1995 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Cornford, F. M., Microcosmograpia Acqademica, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Coughlin, Steve, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Council for International Organizations of Medical Science (CIOMS), 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 56-57)
    - Council, Medical Student, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Council on Goverment Relations (COGR), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Crawley, Francis, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Crowe, Irene, 1987-1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Culliton, Barbara (Medical World News), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Curnen, Mary, 1985, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Cushingham, Judith, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Daar, A.S., 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Danish Council of Ethics, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Dans, Peter E., 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Davidoff, Frank, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Anne, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Dena, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Days, Drew, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - de Abajo, Francisco, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - DeBakey, Lois, 1982-1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - DeCherney, Alan, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Decisions Near the End of Life, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - DeFelice, Stephen, 1989-1996 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Degutis, Linda, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Delph, Yvette, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - DeVita, Vince, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - de Wachter, M., 1979-1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Deykin, David, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Dickens, Bernard, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Diers, Donna, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Djerassi, Carl, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Dommel, F. William, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Donaghue Foundation, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Donaldson, Robert, 1974-1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Donnelly, Strachan, 1988-1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Dowdle, Walter, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Drane, James, 1990-2001 (Box 5, Folder 31-32)
    - Dreyfus, Ruth, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Drickamer, Margaret, 1987-1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Duffy, Tom, 1979-1992 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Dunbar, Geoffrey, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Dunbar, Jackie, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 37-38)
    - Dunbar-Jacobs, Jackie, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Duncan, Brenna, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Dupont, Claire, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Dustan, Harriet, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Dworkin, Jerry, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Edgar, Harold, 1982-1990 (Box 5, Folder 44-45)
    - Elefteriades, John, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Ellenberg, Jonas, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Ellenberg, Susan, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 48-49)
    - Ellis, Gary, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Elmore, Joann, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Elsas, Louis, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Emanuel, Ezekiel (Zeke), 2003 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Emanuel, Ezekiel and Linda Emanuel, 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Emanuel, Linda, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Encyclopedia/Biotechnology, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Encyclopedia 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Endocrine Society, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Endocare, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Energy, Department of, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Engel, Linda, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Engelhardt, Tris, 1985-1999 (Box 5, Folder 62-63)
    - Epstein, Steven, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Ethics consults, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Ethics, programs in, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - European Commission, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Evans, Donald, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Evans, John, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Exiled scientists, Undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Ezekowitz, Mike, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Faden, Ruth, 1976-1992 (Box 5, Folder 72-73)
    - Fallon, Barbara G., 1987-1995 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Farley, Margaret, 1975-1998 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Fauci, Anthony, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
    - Faundes, Anibal, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Fein, Rashi, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Feinberg, Mark, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Feinstein, Alvan R., 1969-1991 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
    - Feldman, Jack, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Fellman, Bruce, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Fetal Tissue Transplantation, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Figueroa, Patricio, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Fine, Eugene, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Fine, Stuart, 1991-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Fineberg, Harvey, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Fischbach, Ruth, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Fischer, David, 1980-1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Fisher, Celia, 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 19-21)
    - Fishman, Lisa, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Flather-Morgan, Alex, 1986-1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Fleischman, Alan, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Fletcher, John, 1975-1996 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Fletcher, Robert, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Fluss, S. S., 1981-1996 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Fogarty International Center, National Institutes of Health, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Workshop, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Foley, Kathleen, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Inspection, 1977-1984 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Inspector, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - NPRM, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Forrest, John, 1974-1994 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Fost, Norman, 1976-1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Fox, Daniel, 1984-1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fox, Ellen, 1980-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fox, Renée C., 1973-1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fracture Intervention Trial, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Frankfurt, Harry, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Franson, Timothy, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Friedland, Gerald, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Friedlander, Gary, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Frommer, Peter, 1967-1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Fuenzalida, Hernan, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Fullilove, Robert, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
    - Gadow, Sally, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Gallin, John, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Galston, Arthur, 1977-1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Gandhi, Rupali, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Gastrointestinal Endoscopy, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Gejman, Pablo, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Gelernter, Joel, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Gellhorn, Alfred, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Genaissance, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Genel, Myron, 1974-1994 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - General Accounting Office, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - George Washington University, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 27-29)
      - Medicine, 1977-1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Gettner, Pat, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Gewirtz, Greg, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Gibbons, Mark, Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Gibson, Susan, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Gifford, Robert, 1977-1989 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Gillis, Norman, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Gillon, Raanan, 1984-1991 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Glantz, Leonard, 1979-1994 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Glick, Shimon, 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Glickman, Mort, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Global Lawyers and Physicians, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Global Strategies, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Conference, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Goldman, Lee, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Goldman, Peter, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Gordon, Martin, 1990-1996 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Gorovitz, Sam, 1984-1998 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Gostin, Larry, 1988-1997 (Box 7, Folder 48-49)
    - Government Reform Committee, Beth Chay, Undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Grady, Christine, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Graf, Leetha, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gray, Bradford, 1971-1995 (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
      - D.C. Children's Hospital site visit, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Grinnell, Fred, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Grodin, Michael, 1986-1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Groton, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Gustafson, James, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Haakonson, Clair, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Haeseler, Rick, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Hailu, Tigist, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Halpern, Jody, 1987-1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Handschumacher, R. E., 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Hanft, Ruth, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Hansen, Helena, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Hartwell, Chad, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Harvard Ethics, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Hastings, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hawkins, Peter, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Hayslett, Joan, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Hayunga, Eugene, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Hazard, Geoffrey, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Heath, Erica, 1978-1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Herbly, Hazem, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Heymann, David, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Higgs, Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Hill, Donald, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Hilleman, Maurice, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Hodel, Derek, 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Hodler, Jürg, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Hoffmaster, Barry, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Holder, Angela, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Hollander, Rachelle, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Holocaust, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Holt, Ellen, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Holton, Gerald, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Hooker, Worthington, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Horowitz, Arthur, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Horwitz, Ralph, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Hoshino, Kai, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - House, Jeffrey, 1991-2000 (Box 8, Folder 43-44)
    - Howarth, Marna, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Howe, Chris, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Howes, Rosemarie, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Human Investigation Committee
      - General, 1988-1998 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Mishkin audit, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Reorganizations and issues, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Humanities in Medicine, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Hunt, Linda, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Hutt, Peter B., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Hutter, Randi, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Ickovics, Jeannette, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - IJsselmuiden, Carel, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Indiana, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Institute of Medicine, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies (ISPS), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Bioethics, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Donaghue agreement, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Ethics, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Institutional Tissue Access and Distribution, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - International Association of Bioethics, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - International Biographical Centre, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - International Centre of Medicine and Law, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN), 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - International Conference on1998 Technical Requirements for Registration of Pharmaceuticals for Human Use (ICH) (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Investigative Medicine, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - IRB-101 at Yale, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CHP), 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Jekel, Jim, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Jimenez, Rosa, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Jonas, Hans, 1979-2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Judith, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Kohar, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Sabra, 1987-1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Jonsen, Albert, S.J., 1974-2000 (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA), 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Journalists, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Jubanyik, Karen, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Kahler, R. L., 1968-1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Kahn, Norm, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Kaiser, Muriel, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Kaldjian, Lauris, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Kantor, F. S., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Kapplan, Samantha, Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Karlawish, Jason, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Kass, Leon, 1980-1991 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Kass, Nancy, 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Katz, Jay, 1973-1996 (Box 9, Folder 22-24)
    - Katz, Susan, 1986-1996 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Kaufman, Sharon, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Kay, Emmanuel M., Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Keiser, Harry, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Kelley, James, Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Kenney, James, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Kessler, David, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 31-32)
    - Keyserlingk, Ted, 1991-1999 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Khazova, Olga, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Kidd, K. K., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Kim, John, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Kimsma, Gerrit K., 1997 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Kimura, Rihito, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Kincaid, Harold, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - King, Patricia, 1975-1989 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Kinsella, Doug, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Kiskaddon, S., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Klaidman, Steve, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Klassen, Gerald, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Kleber, H., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Klin, Ami, Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Knudson, Paula, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Kohlberg, Lawrence, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Kohorn, Ernest, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Kolata, Gina Bari, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Koocher, Gerald P. (Gerry), 1989, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 51-52)
    - Kopelman, Loretta, 1983-1993 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Kosten, Tom, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Krakauer, Eric, 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Kregs, Robert, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Krim, Mathilde, 1986-1991, undated (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
    - Krishnaswamy, Saroja, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Kushner, Thomasina, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Kweder, Sandra, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ladd, John, 1975-1987 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
    - Lamm, Richard, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Langbein, John, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Lange, Robert, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Larsen, David, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Lasagna, Lou, 1973-1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Lasky, Larry, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Last, John, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
    - Lavy, Norman, 1987-1998 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Law, Policy and Ethics (LPE) Core, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Lebacqz, Karen, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Leckman, Jim, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Lederer, Eppie, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Lentz, Tom, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Lerner, A. B., 1965-1994 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Lerner, Seth, 1986-2000 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Levin, Bruce, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Levine, Carol, 1976-1999 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Lewis, Dorothy, 1977-1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Lewis, Mel, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Library Associates (Yale), 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Lidz, Ted, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Lie, Reidar, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Lieberman, Joseph, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lifetime Medical Television, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Lifton, R. J., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Lilly, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Lin, Melody, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Lind, Stuart, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Lindee, Susan, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Lingis, Verna, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Lister, George, 1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Lo, Bernard, 1984-1992 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Loewy, Eric, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Loue, Sana, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Louney, Kurt, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Lovenberg, Tim, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lovenberg, Walter, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Lowenthal, David, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Lowrance, William, 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 50-51)
    - Ludwig, Hans, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Luna, Florencia, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 52A)
    - Lynch, Abbyann, 1990-1999 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Lynch, Heather, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Lynn, Joanne, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Lytton, Bernard, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Mackay, Charles, 1976-1988 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Macklin, Ruth, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - MacQueen, Kate, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Macro International, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Madden, Josh, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Mahoney, M. Jerry, 1974-1989 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Mahowald, Mary, 1981-1992 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Malawesta, Steve, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Manchester Hospital, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Mandell, Harvey, 1979-1994 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Mann, Jonathan, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Mannarino, Maria, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Manniello, Robert, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Manning, Frederick, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Marangopoulos Foundation for Human Rights, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Marchand, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Marcus, Ruth Barcan, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Marcy, Ted, 1987-1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Margolin, Art, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Mariner, Wendy, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Marks, Harry, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Marlink, Richard, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
    - Marmor, Ted, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Marsh, John, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Marshall, Patricia, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Mashaw, Jerry, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Mastroianni, Anna, 1999, undated (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
    - Mattison, Donald, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Maun, Angeli, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - May, William, Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - MCB University Press, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - McCarthy, Charles, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - McCormick, Richard, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - McCullough, Larry, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - McHenry, Christine, 1992-1999 (Box 11, Folder 25-26)
    - McKay, Charles, Circa 1992 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - McMullen, Barbara, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - McNeill, Paul, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - McPhedran, Peter, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - McPherson, Elizabeth, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Mechanic, David, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Medical Research Council of Canada (MRC), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Medical Research Industries, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Medical Tribune, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Medicine in the Public Interest, 1993-2002 (Box 11, Folder 36-38)
    - Mehta, Philip, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Meier, Paul, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Meinert, Curt, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Melchinger, Dave, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Melnick, Vijaya, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Melzer, Leslie, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Mensa, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Merck, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Merman, Alan, 1983-2001 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Merrill, Joe, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Merson, Michael, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 49-50)
    - Merton, Vanessa, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 51-52)
    - Merz, Jon, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Meyer, Monica, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 54-55)
    - Miles Institute, 1991-1996 (Box 11, Folder 56-57)
    - Miles, Steven, 1987-1994 (Box 11, Folder 58-59)
    - Miller, Franklin, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Miller, Robert, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 61-62)
    - Mirkin, Bernard, 1993-1998 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Mishkin, Barbara, 1978-1998 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Mitchell, Charles W., 1983-1991 (Box 11, Folder 65-66)
    - Mitchell, Christine, 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Moazam, Farhat, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Moctezuma Barragan, Gonzalo, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Montana Health, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 70)